<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog name</title>
    <link>http://localhost:3000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:3000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <description>General description of the blog</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 22:11:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en</language>
    <generator>Lume v2.2.2</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Fact check  has become just another word for censorship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<h3 id="prose" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#prose" class="header-anchor">Prose</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2024/10/03/opinion/fact-check-has-become-just-another-word-for-censorship/">https://nypost.com/2024/10/03/opinion/fact-check-has-become-just-another-word-for-censorship/</a></p>
<p>‘Fact check’ has become just another word for censorship</p>
<p>“Fact-checking” is like “fake news”: Something that is now entirely in the eye of the beholder.</p>
<h3 id="fact-checking-becoming-censorship" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#fact-checking-becoming-censorship" class="header-anchor">Fact-Checking Becoming Censorship</a></h3>
<p>Fact-checking has become just another word for censorship. In a recent vice presidential debate, CBS News moderators attempted to fact-check Sen. JD Vance and demonstrated one of the big problems in this media era: they only seemed interested in fact-checking in one direction - against the Republican candidate.</p>
<p>During the debate, moderator Margaret Brennan decided to fact-check something that Vance said and immediately relayed a piece of false information herself. This instance reveals that not only do these &quot;fact-checkers&quot; frequently get their facts wrong, but also they are selective about which facts to correct. In this case, it was clearly against Vance.</p>
<h3 id="issues-with-media's-role-in-fact-checking" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#issues-with-media's-role-in-fact-checking" class="header-anchor">Issues with Media's Role in Fact-Checking</a></h3>
<p>The problem lies in the fact that many media institutions are not competent at determining what is true or false. The era of social media has seen a dilution of power in traditional gatekeepers like newspapers and TV networks. New platforms allow anyone to point out inaccuracies, thereby questioning the previous control over narratives.</p>
<p>Media's Role: Gatekeeper vs. Story Selector</p>
<p>There used to be a time when newspapers could suppress certain stories, but with technological advancements, it is no longer possible to hide everything from the public eye. However, some media houses still try to select what to publish or not publish in order to suit a particular narrative, making them more untrustworthy than ever.</p>
<h3 id="public-awareness-and-perception" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#public-awareness-and-perception" class="header-anchor">Public Awareness and Perception</a></h3>
<p>The public has grown wiser in understanding these strategies. For instance, they can easily find a story that a media house tries to suppress by resorting to alternative platforms. But it also exposes the transparent and increasingly less trustworthy nature of such selective publishing houses.</p>
<p>When it comes to October surprises or other political tactics, people are not easily fooled anymore. They know that these tricks are expected during election times, so they do not fall for them as easily as before.</p>
<h3 id="conclusion" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#conclusion" class="header-anchor">Conclusion</a></h3>
<p>The fact-checking phenomenon has evolved into a tool for censorship in the wrong hands. Media organizations claiming neutrality and fairness often show clear biases or selectivity in their fact-checking approach, making it easier to identify their partisan leanings rather than being seen as unbiased or impartial gatekeepers of information.</p>
<h3 id="image" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#image" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<p><img src="https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2024/10/newspress-collage-j0lto3hrv-1727992491394.jpg?quality=75&amp;strip=all&amp;1727978131&amp;w=1024" alt=""></p>
<p>This image captures a moment from what appears to be a political debate or discussion. The main subject is a man in professional attire, consisting of a dark suit and red tie with an American flag pin on his lapel, suggesting he might be involved in politics or public speaking. He stands against the backdrop of a large screen displaying another individual seated at a desk labeled 'CBS News Vice Presidential Debate'. This suggests that the image is taken during such a political event where media coverage is prominent. The setting indicates a formal and serious atmosphere, typical for televised political events aimed at informing voters about candidates' policies and visions for leadership roles like vice president or higher office.</p>
<h3 id="verse" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#verse" class="header-anchor">Verse</a></h3>
<h3 id="fact-check-censorship" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#fact-check-censorship" class="header-anchor">Fact Check Censorship</a></h3>
<p>In modern days a term has sprung up
To quell all speech that dares to stir and sup,
Yet far from noble or virtuous act,
It serves the powers with views to protect.</p>
<p>This 'fact-checking', like false news of old,
Doth lie in eye beholder to behold.
Once meant to keep the truth above the fray,
Now it's a tool for those in power's play.</p>
<p>No longer is the aim just simple truth
The goal now is the censor's silent oath.
A way to stop all speech that dares annoy,
And force the views of power upon all.</p>
<p>This game was played at VP debate last week,
Where 'fact-checkers' tried one-sided heck.
On Springfield, Ohio, they sought to pounce,
But truth did hide as falsehood took its dance.</p>
<p>Let not us be like birds who tweet and chirp
At those below, while we sit on our perch.
For if we join in this game of hate and scorn,
We play right into the hands of those for whom
This system serves: the powers that be,
Who use it to keep down speech you and I.</p>
<p>So let us seek a higher way than this
Of censuring those who think amiss.
Instead, let reason light our path ahead,
And help us see truth not obscured by dread.
For in the end, 'tis wisdom helps us steer
Away from conflict fueled by fear and ire.</p>
<p>But should we find as one our common core,
Then truth might rise above control's sore fight.</p>
<p>Thus shall we strive to show that speech can soar
Beyond the reach of those who would deplore,
And give to all an ear to think and speak.
That truth might rise unbridled, free and meek.</p>
<p>But if like me you too have played this game,
Then change your tune from scorn to truth's sweet aim.
For in the end our goal should not be strife,
But speech unchained, uncensored, free as life.</p>
<h3 id="" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#" class="header-anchor"></a></h3>
<p>Poem</p>
<h3 id="fact-checking-becoming-censorship-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#fact-checking-becoming-censorship-1" class="header-anchor">Fact-Checking Becoming Censorship</a></h3>
<p>In a time where truth doth hide,
A new tool's risen from the tide.
Fact-checking, once pure and bright,
Has turned its back on right and light.</p>
<p>Through CBS stage, this fact did fall:
Vance was checked by Brennan's call.
But her words, they too, did lie,
Revealing bias, blind eye.</p>
<h3 id="issues-with-media's-role-in-fact-checking-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#issues-with-media's-role-in-fact-checking-1" class="header-anchor">Issues with Media's Role in Fact-Checking</a></h3>
<p>Control once held firm over tale,
Newspapers ruled without bale.
But times have changed, and power's gone,
Each voice can now be heard on.</p>
<p>Gatekeepers turned to story's choice,
Untrustworthy, biased, no surprise.
Yet public knows their games too well,
In transparency they dwell.</p>
<h3 id="public-awareness-and-perception-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#public-awareness-and-perception-1" class="header-anchor">Public Awareness and Perception</a></h3>
<p>They see through masks and lies that tell,
October surprises don't dwell.
No longer fooled by old-time schemes,
Awareness keeps them from the dreams.</p>
<p>Public's grown in wisdom, true,
Knowing tricks are not anew.
Through channels new and various,
Truth seeks pathways disparate.</p>
<h3 id="conclusion-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#conclusion-1" class="header-anchor">Conclusion</a></h3>
<p>Fact-checking, now a tool of shame,
Censorship dressed as virtuous claim.
Media's part doth often blur,
Showing leanings, clear as hurrah!</p>
<p>Unbiased they claim to be,
But fact's twisted truth for all to see.
In selectivity they hide,
Truth's gatekeepers, in decay they slide.</p>
<p><img src="https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2024/10/newspress-collage-j0lto3hrv-1727992491394.jpg?quality=75&amp;strip=all&amp;1727978131&amp;w=1024" alt=""></p>
<h3 id="image-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#image-1" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<h3 id="politics-in-public-view" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/factcheckhasbec-p/#politics-in-public-view" class="header-anchor">Politics in Public View</a></h3>
<p>A man of stance with suit's embrace,
And tie of red to grace his face.
An eagle's banner pin adorns
His lapel, a symbol of the powers that be at norms.</p>
<p>On large screen's stage, 'CBS News Vice'
Is writ as claimant of the dice.
A desk doth sit another there,<br>
For all to view and ponder fair.</p>
<p>Such scenes, they craft the public eye,
In formal setting, high stake's tie.
Where visions grand for leading roles
And policies with voter's souls.</p>
<p>Thus does this shot a moment hold,
Of weighty talk 'tween minds so bold.</p>
<p>Each New Topic.</p>
<pre>Modelfile<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text of any length, punctuated or unpunctuated, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, with nuance about the circumstances of each narrator.

"
Modelfile1<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, converted into rhymed iambic pentameter in the style of Shakespeare.

"
</pre>]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:20:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says he will attend Trump rally in Butler  Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<h3 id="prose" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#prose" class="header-anchor">Prose</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2024/10/04/elon-musk-trump-rally-00182506">https://www.politico.com/news/2024/10/04/elon-musk-trump-rally-00182506</a></p>
<p>Elon Musk says he will attend Trump rally in Butler, Pennsylvania</p>
<p>Trump had vowed to return to the area where he was shot in a failed assassination attempt this summer.</p>
<h3 id="elon-musk-attending-trump-rally-in-butler%2C-pennsylvania" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#elon-musk-attending-trump-rally-in-butler%2C-pennsylvania" class="header-anchor">Elon Musk Attending Trump Rally in Butler, Pennsylvania</a></h3>
<p>Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX, has announced that he will attend Donald Trump's rally in Butler, Pennsylvania on Saturday. This comes after Trump vowed to return to the area where he was shot during a failed assassination attempt in July.</p>
<p>Details surrounding the event are scarce, but it is known that both Trump and Musk have had an increasing presence on social media and public events recently. Musk has been very critical of Democrats lately, despite previously supporting them.</p>
<p>The pair's relationship seems to be growing stronger as they appear together more often in person, having held a virtual interview on X (formerly Twitter) which experienced technical difficulties but is still remembered for its historical nature.</p>
<p>Topics to discuss:</p>
<ul>
<li>The implications of Elon Musk attending Trump's rally</li>
<li>The growing closeness between the two and their political views</li>
<li>How this will impact both Trump's campaign and Musk's public image</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="image" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#image" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<p><img src="https://static.politico.com/b1/8a/1306354a468aba78a81a637c2afc/https-delivery-gettyimages.com/downloads/1258741771" alt=""></p>
<p>In this image, a man is captured in what appears to be an interview setting. He's dressed formally in a dark suit and white shirt with his microphone clipped onto the lapel of his jacket, hinting at a professional or public speaking engagement. His posture suggests he’s engaged in conversation, possibly answering questions about technology-related topics given some text visible in the background referencing Tesla cars and solar energy technologies. The image evokes an atmosphere of seriousness and importance.</p>
<h3 id="verse" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#verse" class="header-anchor">Verse</a></h3>
<h3 id="topic-1%3A-elon-musk-attending-trump-rally" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#topic-1%3A-elon-musk-attending-trump-rally" class="header-anchor">Topic 1: Elon Musk Attending Trump Rally</a></h3>
<p>In a surprising turn,<br>
Elon Musk will attend the rally.<br>
Where Trump was shot before,<br>
The billionaire CEO will venture more.</p>
<p>His support for the Donald, strong and true,<br>
To honor Corey Comperatore's memory too.<br>
A day to fight and stand united,<br>
Musk joins the fray with his own credibility.</p>
<p>Trump's running mate Vance will be there as well,<br>
GOP Senators in tow like a shining spell.<br>
Musk's journey from Democrat to Trump's man,<br>
A transformation that no one could plan.</p>
<p>This rally marks the start of a new era,<br>
Where two business minds converge and say &quot;hear&quot;.<br>
Elon Musk attending Trump's event in Butler, PA,<br>
A testament to how political winds can blow.</p>
<h3 id="topic-2%3A-the-assasination-attempt" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#topic-2%3A-the-assasination-attempt" class="header-anchor">Topic 2: The Assasination Attempt</a></h3>
<p>On summer days when shots rang out,<br>
In Pennsylvania Trump's rally was brought.<br>
To a halt by danger and fear,<br>
A moment that changed the rest of the year.</p>
<p>Trump vowed to return to that spot,<br>
Where tragedy struck like a sharp-cut note.<br>
Honor for Corey Comperatore's soul,<br>
And bravery of those injured - his resolve to uphold.</p>
<p>The attempt on Trump's life was real and stark,<br>
But he returned where danger did marck.<br>
A symbol of resilience, of not backing down,<br>
In Butler Pennsylvania the crowd will gather now.</p>
<h3 id="topic-3%3A-musk's-political-evolution" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#topic-3%3A-musk's-political-evolution" class="header-anchor">Topic 3: Musk's Political Evolution</a></h3>
<p>Kamala Harris once was seen as far left by him,<br>
Musk's views have transformed in a whimsical spin.<br>
From Biden votes to Trump rallies he goes,<br>
A journey that few could understand or chose.</p>
<p>His tweets about government and immigration,<br>
Echoing the conservative narrative it brings.<br>
An immigrant himself now a key player,<br>
In America PAC with funds to shower.</p>
<p>The relationship between Musk and Trump,<br>
Blossoming in public eyes like never before.<br>
A partnership of business minds and political will,<br>
Musk's journey from left to right, we can all hear.</p>
<p>This topic concludes the provided text. The rhymed iambic pentameter style mirrors Shakespearean verse, capturing the essence of each part.</p>
<h3 id="" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#" class="header-anchor"></a></h3>
<p>Poem</p>
<h3 id="elon-musk-attending-trump-rally-in-butler%2C-pennsylvania-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#elon-musk-attending-trump-rally-in-butler%2C-pennsylvania-1" class="header-anchor">Elon Musk Attending Trump Rally in Butler, Pennsylvania</a></h3>
<p>In realms of politics and industry's might,
Two Titans meet, their paths entwined tonight.
Elon Musk, CEO of SpaceX grand,
Shall at Donald Trump's rally take a stand.</p>
<p>This event, held in Butler, Penn,
Where Trump himself did narrowly fend
An assassin's bullet, summer past,
Now seeks to reclaim his former cast.</p>
<p>Details are few, but one thing is clear:
Both men have made their presence dear.
On social spheres they've left their mark,
With views and posts that leave no spark.</p>
<p>Musk, once a Democrat's friend and aide,
Now turns critical eye on party's creed.
Their paths entwine as they publicly tread
The political stage, both strong and stead.</p>
<p>How shall this union shape the view?
Of Trump's campaign, Musk's public virtue too.
Their joint appearance may stir the ground,
As masses speculate what will be found.</p>
<p><img src="https://static.politico.com/b1/8a/1306354a468aba78a81a637c2afc/https-delivery-gettyimages.com/downloads/1258741771" alt=""></p>
<h3 id="image-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#image-1" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<h3 id="the-formal-interview" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/elonmusksayshew-p/#the-formal-interview" class="header-anchor">The Formal Interview</a></h3>
<p>A man stands tall, his suit a darkened hue,
And white shirt gleams, beneath a clip of blue.
The mic atop his jacket sits with care,
As if for speech or news from fair to foul.</p>
<p>His stance suggests a question being met,
Or tale of tech, that captures yet
The mind's attention on topics grand,
Of Tesla cars and solar lands.</p>
<p>An aura fills the space 'round him cast,
That brooks no jests or frivolous chat.
For here is found a man with purpose lined,
To speak what matters in his time.</p>
<p>This image then, a scene of weight,
Where words and wisdom hold their fate.</p>
<pre>Modelfile<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text of any length, punctuated or unpunctuated, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, with nuance about the circumstances of each narrator.

"
Modelfile1<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, converted into rhymed iambic pentameter in the style of Shakespeare.

"
</pre>]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:20:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard  THIS is why JD Vance DOMINATED Tim Walz in VP Debate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<h3 id="prose" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#prose" class="header-anchor">Prose</a></h3>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5sXsERIRlTU">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5sXsERIRlTU</a></p>
<p>Tulsi Gabbard: THIS is why JD Vance DOMINATED Tim Walz in VP Debate</p>
<p>Tulsi Gabbard breaks down why JD Vance's total dismantling of Tim Walz during last night's VP Debate. Gabbard highlights Vance's command over the issues and ...</p>
<h3 id="tulsi-gabbard-on-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#tulsi-gabbard-on-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate" class="header-anchor">Tulsi Gabbard on JD Vance's Victory in VP Debate</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Tulsi Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman and vice presidential candidate, praises Republican senator JD Vance for his performance during a recent vice presidential debate against Democrat Tim Walz. Gabbard highlights Vance's ability to discuss issues in a relatable way that reflects the policies both he and President Trump support.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gabbard suggests that those who watched the debate with an open mind might have developed a more positive impression of Vance and his policies compared to what they previously knew or believed, partly due to media bias.</li>
<li>She contrasts the approach of Vance and President Trump with that of Democratic candidates like Kamala Harris, implying their policies are less relatable and disconnected from average Americans' struggles.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="the-significance-of-free-speech-in-the-election" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-significance-of-free-speech-in-the-election" class="header-anchor">The Significance of Free Speech in the Election</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Gabbard emphasizes the importance of free speech in the election, citing censorship issues under the current administration. She questions Tim Walz's stance on free speech, suggesting a double standard where certain speech is protected while others are banned.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gabbard highlights how censorship extends to personal attacks and misinformation from political rivals.</li>
<li>She argues that protecting every American's right to free speech is crucial for maintaining a democratic republic.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="the-importance-of-taking-responsibility" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-importance-of-taking-responsibility" class="header-anchor">The Importance of Taking Responsibility</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Gabbard criticizes politicians who try to dismiss their mistakes or wrongdoings, stating that true leadership requires owning up to errors and being accountable.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>She uses Tim Walz's performance in the debate as an example, suggesting he should have taken responsibility for his party's policies rather than trying to defend them.</li>
<li>Gabbard implies that such behavior reflects poorly on leaders and contributes to a lack of trust in political figures.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="free-speech-and-political-retaliation" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#free-speech-and-political-retaliation" class="header-anchor">Free Speech and Political Retaliation</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Gabbard discusses the personal significance of free speech, mentioning her own experience with being placed on a domestic terror watch list (Quiet Skies) after criticizing Kamala Harris. She mentions ongoing legal actions and support from organizations like ACLJ.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gabbard implies that many Americans, including those not in the public eye, have been wrongly targeted by the current administration due to their political views and exercise of free speech.</li>
<li>She suggests that this issue extends beyond just being able to say what you want without censorship, but also includes government retaliation against those who speak out.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="appreciation-for-courageous-voices" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#appreciation-for-courageous-voices" class="header-anchor">Appreciation for Courageous Voices</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Gabbard expresses gratitude towards Bobby Kennedy and others for their bravery in standing up against political persecution and censorship. She appreciates their efforts in defending free speech.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gabbard emphasizes solidarity among Americans, regardless of differing views, to stand together on issues like free speech.</li>
<li>She suggests that voting for Donald Trump in the election is a choice for those who believe strongly in free speech.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="updates-on-government-targeting" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#updates-on-government-targeting" class="header-anchor">Updates on Government Targeting</a></h3>
<p>Detailed Text of the Topic:
Gabbard updates her audience on the status of government targeting post her criticism of Kamala Harris. She mentions Federal Air Marshal whistleblowers and their exposure of the Quiet Skies program, putting her name on a domestic terror watch list.</p>
<p>Nuance:</p>
<ul>
<li>Gabbard expresses hope that Congress will take up this issue.</li>
<li>She highlights ongoing legal actions, working with J Seculo and ACLJ, and suggests many Americans are being wrongfully targeted for political views and exercise of free speech.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="conclusion" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#conclusion" class="header-anchor">Conclusion</a></h3>
<p>Gabbard's commentary covers several key points in the context of a vice presidential debate between JD Vance and Tim Walz. Her focus on free speech, government retaliation, and the need for accountability among politicians provides nuance to her perspective on the election. She expresses gratitude towards others' efforts in defending these rights and shares updates on her own experiences with political targeting.</p>
<h3 id="image" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#image" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5sXsERIRlTU/maxresdefault.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>The image is a split-screen screenshot from Blaze Media, featuring two individuals presumably engaged in a live discussion. On the left side of the screen, there's a man with white hair and beard, dressed in a grey suit and blue tie, pointing assertively as he speaks. His background appears to be an indoor setting with warm lighting, possibly at a restaurant or bar given its ambiance.</p>
<p>On the right side, we see a woman with long dark hair styled down. She is wearing a navy-blue blazer adorned with decorative gold buttons and holds up what seems like golden coins in her hand as she talks animatedly. The background here suggests an office-like environment filled with bookshelves packed tightly with books of various colors.</p>
<p>The text overlay on the screen provides additional context: 'GET $40 OFF A 1-YEAR SUBSCRIPTION...USE CODE DEBATE AT BLAZEDEBATE.COM' indicating a promotional message likely tied to Blaze Media’s subscription services. This setup suggests that the image captures a segment from a debate or discussion show hosted by Blaze Media, aimed at engaging viewers with insightful commentary and promotions.</p>
<h3 id="verse" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#verse" class="header-anchor">Verse</a></h3>
<h3 id="tulsi-gabbard's-analysis-of-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#tulsi-gabbard's-analysis-of-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate" class="header-anchor">Tulsi Gabbard's Analysis of JD Vance's Victory in VP Debate</a></h3>
<p>In iambic pentameter:
Tulsi Gabbard speaks, her words alight,
With truth unbound, like flames against the night.
Her gaze upon the stage, a piercing sight,
Where Vance and Walz did clash their views in flight.</p>
<p>A Democrat she stands, but not confined
To party lines; her vision broad and kind.
For those who seek Trump's vote to find,
In Vance's command, an answer primed.</p>
<p>The issues wrestled 'twixt the candidates,
Did leave the minds of viewers recompensed.
A different view on policies defended,
With positive impact, their thoughts endorsed.</p>
<p>But media's role, a bias undenied,
In pockets deep of Harris' campaign tied.
Vance's talk, a reflection of the real,
To people's needs and Trump's aims appealed.</p>
<p>Contrasted with what came from Clinton's heir,
The promises and arrogance laid bare.
Yet Walz did struggle in defense so rare,
His words, a tough job but ill-prepared.</p>
<p>The moment that crystallized all tonight?
The censorship under Harris brought to light.
A double standard, the free speech fight,
Vance's stance on what's right shone bright.</p>
<p>And Gabbard, though dismayed at current state,
Believes in Trump and freedom's weight.
The issues, from economy to hate,
Reveal a choice that must be debated.</p>
<p>In voting Trump, Americans see,
A chance to stand for what matters thee.</p>
<h3 id="" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#" class="header-anchor"></a></h3>
<p>Poem</p>
<h3 id="tulsi-gabbard-on-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#tulsi-gabbard-on-jd-vance's-victory-in-vp-debate-1" class="header-anchor">Tulsi Gabbard on JD Vance's Victory in VP Debate</a></h3>
<p>Forsooth, a tale of triumph told,
Of Vance who faced debate's fold.
Tulsi Gabbard's praise doth swell,
His words, like arrows from the hell.</p>
<p>Commanding issues, he did show,
The policies that Trump did know.
With relatable speech and spell,
He turned many hearts to dwell.</p>
<p>But media bias, a shadow cast,
Distorted truth, as time hath past.
Open minds to Vance were drawn,
By his honest ways, like morning's dawn.</p>
<p>Contrast of approaches clear to see,
Vance and Trump, more free than key.
Harris and kin, distant, cold,
Their struggles not by stories told.</p>
<h3 id="the-significance-of-free-speech-in-the-election-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-significance-of-free-speech-in-the-election-1" class="header-anchor">The Significance of Free Speech in the Election</a></h3>
<p>Free speech, a gem that we must hold,
For without it, truth is sold.
In elections past, Gabbard did declare,
Walz's stance unclear, or so we fare.</p>
<p>Yet, a double standard we see,
Some words protected, some to be.
While others banned by decree,
A free republic, thus we flee.</p>
<p>Censorship too, in personal attack,
And misinformation cast back.
For all must speak what lies within,
Or our democracy shall lose its skin.</p>
<h3 id="the-importance-of-taking-responsibility-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-importance-of-taking-responsibility-1" class="header-anchor">The Importance of Taking Responsibility</a></h3>
<p>Leadership's mark, it doth require,
To take the blame and be sincere.
Tim Walz, thy policies were laid bare,
Yet deflected, like a knight in scare.</p>
<p>True leaders own their misdeeds done,
Accountability must be spun.
For trust is lost when errors swept away,
And thus our faith shall fade each day.</p>
<h3 id="free-speech-and-political-retaliation-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#free-speech-and-political-retaliation-1" class="header-anchor">Free Speech and Political Retaliation</a></h3>
<p>Gabbard's plight, a tale of woe,
Placed on list for words once spoken low.
Quiet Skies program did unfold,
A story of control, a tale untold.</p>
<p>ACLJ by her side stood strong,
As battles in courts became the song.
Many others wrongfully targeted were,
By government hands that sought to steer.</p>
<p>Free speech extended beyond just say,
But retaliation's hand to swayed.
We must stand together, hearts and minds,
For truth's sake we shall not resign.</p>
<h3 id="appreciation-for-courageous-voices-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#appreciation-for-courageous-voices-1" class="header-anchor">Appreciation for Courageous Voices</a></h3>
<p>Bobby Kennedy's name, a beacon bright,
Courage against persecution he did fight.
Gabbard's gratitude flows wide,
For those who in defense did reside.</p>
<p>Solidarity amongst Americans,
On free speech our trust must rest.
Vote Trump if thou believest true,
In liberty and all it stood to.</p>
<h3 id="updates-on-government-targeting-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#updates-on-government-targeting-1" class="header-anchor">Updates on Government Targeting</a></h3>
<p>The tale of Gabbard, still unfolds,
Against Kamala's wrath once told.
Federal Air Marshals' whistleblowers came,
Quiet Skies exposed, a program named.</p>
<p>Congress, we hope shall heed the call,
For many Americans stand small.
With J Seculo and ACLJ's aid,
We fight for rights once betrayed.</p>
<p>And so concludes this tale of strife,
Of free speech battles against life.
Gabbard's insights guide us through,
In trust and truth, there is but one hue.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5sXsERIRlTU/maxresdefault.jpg" alt=""></p>
<h3 id="image-1" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#image-1" class="header-anchor">Image</a></h3>
<h3 id="the-man-in-grey" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-man-in-grey" class="header-anchor">The Man in Grey</a></h3>
<p>A man of age, with hair so white,
In grey he stands, adorned with might.
His eyes ablaze, his words precise,
With every point, he claims the prize.</p>
<p>He gestures forth, with hand extended wide,
As if to grasp the truth that lies inside.
His voice, a clarion call, does sound,
The premises he builds on solid ground.</p>
<h3 id="the-woman-in-blue" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-woman-in-blue" class="header-anchor">The Woman in Blue</a></h3>
<p>Beside him stands a woman fair,
Her hair flows down like ebony's sheave.
In blue she shines, with buttons gold,
Each word spoken, like stories old.</p>
<p>With golden coins she gestures, too,
To show the worth of what she drew.
Her talk so lively, words do fly,
Like birds in sky, under the sky.</p>
<h3 id="the-setting-twin" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-setting-twin" class="header-anchor">The Setting Twin</a></h3>
<p>Two worlds collide in split-screen view,
A bar or restaurant for him true,
For her an office space, where thoughts expand,
Books stacked high, as if to demand.</p>
<h3 id="the-show's-endgame" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/url/54tulsigabbardt-p/#the-show's-endgame" class="header-anchor">The Show's Endgame</a></h3>
<p>'Use code Debate,' so they say,
To get $40 off, what a display!
Blaze Media's show, a mix of jest and lore,
With offers sweet, like honey on the shore.</p>
<pre>Modelfile<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text of any length, punctuated or unpunctuated, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, with nuance about the circumstances of each narrator.

"
Modelfile1<br>
FROM hermes3:latest
PARAMETER temperature 1
PARAMETER num_ctx 8192
SYSTEM "You are presented with text, often with multiple topics. You answer strictly in the following format:

### Each New Topic.

Detailed Text of the Topic, converted into rhymed iambic pentameter in the style of Shakespeare.

"
</pre>]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:19:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to install this theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/instructions/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/posts/instructions/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p><strong>Simple blog</strong> is a clean and minimal blog theme for Lume, with support for
tags and authors. It allows to build your own blog <strong>in seconds</strong>, providing
also support for RSS.</p>
<!--more-->
<p>To use it, just import the theme in your <code>_config.ts</code> file:</p>
<pre><code class="language-js">import lume from &quot;lume&quot;;
import blog from &quot;https://deno.land/x/lume_theme_simple_blog/mod.ts&quot;;

const site = lume();
site.use(blog());

export default site;
</code></pre>
<h2 id="customization" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/instructions/#customization" class="header-anchor">Customization</a></h2>
<div class="markdown-alert markdown-alert-tip">
<p class="markdown-alert-title">Tip</p>
<p>You can use <a href="https://lume.land/cms">lumeCMS</a> to customize the blog and add
content easily</p>
</div>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is a post with mastodon comments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews.
Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to
further the overall value proposition. Organically grow the holistic world view
of disruptive innovation via workplace diversity and empowerment.</p>
<!--more-->
<pre><code class="language-js">// this is a command
function myCommand() {
  let counter = 0;

  counter++;
}

// Test with a line break above this line.
console.log(&quot;Test&quot;);
</code></pre>
<p>Bring to the table win-win survival strategies to ensure proactive domination.
At the end of the day, going forward, a new normal that has evolved from
generation X is on the runway heading towards a streamlined cloud solution. User
generated content in real-time will have multiple touchpoints for offshoring.</p>
<h2 id="section-header" tabindex="-1"><a href="http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/#section-header" class="header-anchor">Section Header</a></h2>
<p>Capitalize on low hanging fruit to identify a ballpark value added activity to
beta test. Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from
DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the
loop on focusing solely on the bottom line.</p>
<p>Here is a footnote reference,<sup><a class="footnote-ref" href="http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/#fn-1" id="fnref-1">1</a></sup> and <sup><a class="footnote-ref" href="http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/#fn-2" id="fnref-2">2</a></sup>another. And this<sup><a class="footnote-ref" href="http://localhost:3000/posts/firstpost/#fn-3" id="fnref-3">3</a></sup> is a long note.</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>